Adam Christopher Cooke

329937 Georgia Tech Station, Atlanta, GA 30332 · acooke6@gatech.edu · (321)-271-1283

Professional Overview

Highly motivated student-athlete at the Georgia Institute of Technology majoring in Computer Science with a minor in Leadership Studies. Heavily involved in school extracurricular activities and has held a co-op position that has delivered experience in software engineering while contributing to software systems deployed in Afghanistan. Developed excellent time management, team-oriented, problem-solving, analytical and communication skills, while learning and practicing various software engineering concepts and algorithms as a student, co-op, and student assistant coach.

Skills

- **Programming:** Java, C, Python, as well as familiarity with Git, Android SDK and HTML/CSS
- Other: Excellent time management, team-oriented, problem-solving, analytical and communication skills

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology, College of Computing

Atlanta, Georgia

Candidate for Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Expected May 2016

- Concentration in information internetworks and systems and architecture with a minor in leadership studies.
- GPA 3.52
- Dean's List (all semesters from Fall 2011 Present)
- Studied abroad in Barcelona, Spain during the Summer 2013 Semester

Work Experience

Georgia Tech Research Institute Co-Op Student

Atlanta, GA

May 2012 – Present

- Contributed to applications deployed in Afghanistan as a member of the Tactical Embedded Systems Branch.
- Developed a program for the I-BESS (Integrated Blast Environment Sensor Suite) system that shows what is going on in real time, as well as graphs trends of the collected data.
- Performed system integration tests and acceptance tests on software systems before they were sent to the field.

Volunteer Experience

Georgia Tech Yellow Jackets Cross Country and Track and Field Manager and Student Assistant

Atlanta, Georgia

January 2012 - Present

- Volunteer as team manager to the distance squad of the Georgia Tech cross country and track and field team.
- Assist Coach Alan Drosky in setting up drills, timing and recording workouts for twenty hours of practice time each week.
- Assist in the inventory of team apparel and equipment.

Georgia Tech, College of Computing

Atlanta, Georgia

Mentor

July 2013 - Present

- Mentored nine incoming freshman with the goal of helping them adjust to Georgia Tech and the College of Computing.
- Answered questions and provided insight on courses, career development and extracurricular activities
- Helped organize monthly events for all freshmen within the College of Computing.